[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay, now I wanna do one last thing,
好 这里我要做最后一件事情
because it will be just fun, and then we can all be excited.
因为这个只是好玩 而且我们都会很兴奋
So what I did here, query on a particular car for a particular image.
所以 我要做的是 查询一个特别的汽车来获取一张特别的图片
Let's create a function that does all of that and we can create anytime I want.
让我们创建一个可以完成一切的函数 而且任何时候我们都可以创建它
And so this will be kind
因此这会是个有点
of a fun thing to do.
有趣的事情
So, just for fun,
那么 为了好玩
let's create a lambda to find and
来创建一个lambda函数 来找到和
show nearest neighbor images.
显示最近邻的图片
So, this is a little bit of Python trickery.
这是个Python小技巧
We get to play with it together.
我们一起来尝试它
So, we're gonna call this lambda.
我们称之为lambda
Find, no, just go directly to show.
找到 哦不 直接展示
Show_neighbors and
show_neighbors而且
this is gonna be a lambda and it's gonna take the index i of the image.
这个将是个lambda表达式 参数为图片的索引表下标i
And here it is what it's gonna do.
这就是我要做的
It's going to do exactly what we saw.
它正在按照我们看到的方式进行
So it's gonna get images from IDs, query the nearestneighbor model,
通过id获取图片 查询knn_model
but instead of query for car, let's query from image train of i to i plus one.
但并不是查询车辆 而是查找位于image_train第i位与第i+1位之间的那辆
And then we're gonna take the image and we're gonna call .show in it.
而后 我们获取图片且调用.show函数
This is a crazy long lambda.
这是个非常长的lambda表达式
But after we created it, we can do something pretty neat with it.
但是创建了之后 我们可以非常灵巧得使用它
So now, I can just call show_neighbors and
现在我们调用show_neighbors且
I give it the index of the car which was eight, and
我传入红色汽车的索引表下标8 然后
if you scroll down, you'll see those red cars.
如果你向下滚动 你会看到红色的车辆
Really cool.
真的酷
Now, we can call show_neighbors with some other image.
现在我们可以调用show_neighbors查找其他图片
I actually haven't thought about or played with this, I just made this lambda
实际上我之前没想过或者测试过 然后就创建了这个lambda函数
up together, so actually, I haven't, let's just try and run numbers.
来整合一切 所以实际上 我没尝试过 让我们尝试其他数字
So, how about number 26?
那么 26如何?
So now it's gonna find the neighbors that even know what it is,
所以现在它可以找到邻居们 甚至知道具体内容
26 is this car over here.
26号是这里的车
Actually let me make this a little bigger, so we can all see.
来把它变大一些方便看清
So show neighbors of 26 is this blue car.
那么展示的26号的邻居是这辆蓝色汽车
This assigns a few other cars, which is pretty cool.
同样很酷地指定了一些其他汽车
Let's pick some other number, show_neighbors
来选取一些其他数字 show_neighbors
of these 2,000 images maybe image 1222.
在2000张图片里 可以是第1222号图片
I actually don't know what that would be, but now we can see, oh it's a bird.
我实际上不知道会出现什么 但是现在可以看到 啊 是只鸟
And, you find the nearest neighbors, oh,
而且你找到了最近邻
birds and they'll all similar kind of poses.
一些鸟而且它们处在相似的姿势下
And I know that this is kind of a Ostrich heads and thses other kinds of birds.
而且我知道这是一种鸵鸟的头 以及相似类的鸟
But, they're all birds, which is pretty cool and
但是它们都是鸟类 这点很酷
remember we're just using those deep features.
记住我们现在只是用这些深度特征
And now for the last one, so show_neighbors and
现在作为最后一个 show_neighbors且
you can play with all of this at home.
你可以在电脑上随意尝试
Let's show neighbors of image 2,000.
让我们看看第2000张的近邻们
Oops, Shift+Enter and what are the neighbors of image 2000?
哎呦 Shift+Enter 第2000张的邻居是什么呢?
Okay, you have a car.
好了 你有了辆汽车
It got confused.
有点令人困惑
It got an ostrich but the the rest were all cars.
有一张鸵鸟但是其他的都是汽车
So simple pictures work quite well at image retrieval.
所以简单的图片在图片检索中表现不错
You saw I made one mistake in the few examples that we tried.
你看到了 我尝试的样例里出现了一个错误
But it actually gives you really good results and really nice performance.
但是它实际上给了你很好的结果以及表现
And it was never trained on this dataset, on this images.
而且这个从没在该训练集或该图片上做训练
The images were different sizes, different categories, but
图片有不同的尺寸种类 但是
it still worked quite well and quite exciting.
它仍然运行得不错且非常振奋人心
So these are tools and
这些工具
techniques that can be used in a wide range of areas in a really exciting way.
以及技术可以通过激动人心的方式应用到广泛的领域中
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community